[Soft instrumental music]
A closer look at life. Explore biological structures and processes.
From the cell to its inner world. A representative plant cell.
Bacterium. An educational model of a Gram-negative rod.
Fungi. Explore a representative yeast cell.
Paramecium. One cell, many specialized functions.
Beyond cells. The architecture of a T2 bacteriophage.
Rotate. Look inside. Take it apart. Explore mitochondrial structure.
Make biological processes visible. Transcription: the making of RNA.
From light energy to the chemistry of life. Photosynthesis.
From genetic information to protein. Ribosomal translation.
The details of life are worth a closer look. BioScape, created by Kun Qian.